"0"	"0"	"@maggieatlas I'm using app on iPhone btw""
"+"	"1"	"Yooooooo they got red iphone now ????""
"-"	"-5"	"my phone isn't charging, i'm getting annoyed.i hate my iPhone it's been acting up for the past week ?????""
"-"	"-1"	"You can charge your iPad with a iPhone charger""
"0"	"0"	"@geekanoids i have never brought a iPhone of Apple website do you have to pay a upfront cost because i will pay monthly""
"0"	"0"	"I want the red iPhone ??""
"+"	"1"	"Okaaay, my iPhone fell, shet.""
"-"	"-1"	"It's doesn't matter that all of you iPhone users had these before men the 'lowly' Android user. Got 'em now ??""
"0"	"0"	"@AskFirstTech Neither ApplePay nor First Tech App seem to work on iPhone 7.  Suggestions?""
"-"	"-1"	"I can't get iPhone plus cause my hands already struggle with the 6s????""
"0"	"0"	"My dad has an IPhone ??""
"-"	"-1"	"@KINGofTHIGHHIGH not when your galaxy s7 broke so you're on a 6 1/2 year iPhone 4s with 5gb of total storage, 100mb of available""
"0"	"0"	"I just found out you can draw in your notes on iphone what""
"+"	"1"	"I was thinking about getting an iPhone but not sure what storage size, zip stream music, don't d/like music/ shows just take a lot of pics""
"0"	"0"	"Debating on if i should get the iPhone 7?that camera clean""
"0"	"0"	"I can't believe I'm getting the iPhone 26 ? ?  shdnfmlskfjjs""
"0"	"0"	"Ideas for a protective case for an iPhone 7plus? I'm leaning towards a lifeproof bc slim &waterproof, but it's hard to hear ppl on the phone""
"0"	"0"	"Iphone app draft: JGdCscITx""
"0"	"0"	"Sure I may have regretted getting a 16 gig iPhone but I'll make the best of it by downloading smaller Twitter/Facebook apps.""
"+"	"1"	"Why am I seeing shit about an iPhone 8?? Apple needs to take a vacation. Y'all needa relax.""
"0"	"0"	"So last night I thought I lost my phone... I used a strangers to look for it on find my iPhone & then danced with him ? forgot about it for""
"0"	"0"	"Premium Leather Black Cover CaseAvailable for iPhone 7 and 7 plusTo know price@Sabka Sabkuch""
"0"	"0"	"@a_Suman_ he he iPhone 7 red thepisthar amo anukuna ???? @kinnu3""
"+"	"1"	"@Iwaysgetcurved that's the best feature on my iPhone""
"0"	"0"	"#Top3Apps mentre #papamilano2017 divenne in TendenzaTwitter for iPhone 28%Twitter Web Client 24%Twitter for Android 21%""
"0"	"0"	"@akaKatieMartin who is iphone""
"-"	"-1"	"i need a iphone charger ??""
"-"	"-2"	"my bestfriend got her red iphone ? can't fwIt ... that white screen ugly""
"0"	"0"	"but mine is a 64gb iphone 6s which costs me a total of ?10 a month so idk if it's worth getting any repairs""
"0"	"0"	"Will have to make do with a glitchy iPhone stream. Abysmal service from Sky Go. Now, lets go Seb! #AusGP""
"0"	"0"	"@VideoWord having an iphone is better opsec ?""
"0"	"0"	"@sprintcare Two, we were lead to believe that once our leasing contract was over that the buying of the iPhone fees would be deduced ....""
"0"	"0"	"@realDonaldTrump If you want an abortion, pay for it yourself.Don't know the cost but prob less than an iPhone or car pmt. Choices ladies.""
"0"	"0"	"I kinda want that red iPhone""
"0"	"0"	"On what device do you think Trump tweets from? An iPhone SE? iPad mini? Maybe uses Siri to do a speech-to-text tweet?""
"+"	"2"	"if anything i used it as an excuse to look at iphone 7's lmao""
"0"	"0"	"Ready to get my iPhone on Monday""
"0"	"0"	"Need dat red iPhone 7""
"0"	"0"	"GET YOUR IPHONE NOW! MURANG MURA NALANG SYA! DON'T WORRY IT'S 100% ORIG. PM ME! ??""
"-"	"-2"	"Am I obnoxious enough to buy the iPhone 7+ tomorrow?""
"0"	"0"	"Just got a new iPhone 7 and this phone is everything""
"0"	"0"	"I WANT A RED IPHONE. ????""
"0"	"0"	"iPhone 7 plus im cumin get yu""
"0"	"0"	"@EveryApplePro plz select me for red iphone giveaway""
"0"	"0"	"yo iphone no case slippery""
"0"	"0"	"Eh if the iPhone 7 product red was all red instead of a white front I would have copped it.""
"0"	"0"	"@sprintcare we were not informed that only one iPhone for the two on the plan would be 16GB, & the other was 64GB""
"0"	"0"	"@patcgeorges IPhone?.""
"+"	"1"	"@EveryApplePro I just really wish that mr. EAP can pick me. I've been searching my whole life just to find an iPhone. God Bless.""
"-"	"-1"	"This iPhone update is trash ?""
"0"	"0"	"I tweeted this so yall know I have a iphone 7.""
"0"	"0"	"Why my iphone die faster than my Apple Watch does? ??""
"0"	"0"	"Hopefully they still have the red iPhone 7 plus by wed""
"0"	"0"	"Once I tell myself not to to get an iPhone because it's just a phone! Now I guess mmg betul orang kata "Tuhan duga apa kita cakap" ?""
"0"	"0"	"Kade got an iPhone and all he wants to do now is play me in the iMessage games ??????""
"-"	"-4"	"Do people still play words with friends? I got the iPhone too late in 2012 and missed out on that. Sad!""
"-"	"-1"	"@manasvaze connected iPhone to Mac and launched QuickTime. Then File > new vide record > video source > iPhone""
"-"	"-1"	"when you badly want the iphone 7+ but you also think that the idea of removing the headphone jack is so dumb ?""
"0"	"0"	"@OneChilledBeer Plus @anaggh s #iphone has lost the feel on the S @girishmallya""
"0"	"0"	"@tldtoday plz select me for iphone giveaway""
"+"	"1"	"@denzzzel *** & a red iPhone""
"+"	"1"	"@rachel_pick also, cool. I have a beard & iPhone. phewww""
"0"	"0"	"Kinda want the Red iPhone 7plus???""
"-"	"-1"	"yo f*** iphone 7 bro,my shit broke in just 3 weeks?""
"0"	"0"	"#Top3Apps for 'Jackpot En Poy'Twitter for Android 50%Twitter for iPhone 15%Twitter Web Client 14%""
"-"	"-1"	"iPhone gang but all kinda shit on my Motorola ?""
"0"	"0"	"@jasoninthehouse Haven't seen or heard from you during the ACA campaign, IPhone not working? We won't forget, sell the parks while you can.""
"-"	"-2"	"iPhone batteries are shit my phone will be at 40% and in 5 minutes will go to 27% tf and i got a 6s Plus it gets annoying""
"0"	"0"	"Another thing, if I buy the red iPhone , it's gonna get cracked in a week. Why buy a case for a all red phone ?""
"0"	"0"	"I want the red iPhone ???""
"+"	"1"	"Every part of me wants the iPhone 7 Plus (PRODUCT)RED. But like, I already bought myself a birthday present...""
"0"	"0"	"@WorkflowHQ it’s crashing before even loads for first time. Tried installing again from app store. Running on ios 10.2 and iPhone 7plus""
"0"	"0"	"People I Don't Have A iPhone Stop Asking For me to face time""
"+"	"2"	"#NowPlaying for iPhonehide?EYES LOVE YOU?""
"+"	"1"	"Kermit uses iPhone now though lol.""
"0"	"0"	"Does anyone have an iPhone 7 PLUS?""
"+"	"2"	"The iPhone Era has ended for me... back to the Droid! Wow what a difference lol""
"0"	"0"	"#iBooksAuthor, Contents of media located in same page start seamlessly in iPad. but each content stands up with other window with #iPhone""
"-"	"-5"	"I'm low key cheating myself by still having the iPhone 5s ?? I'll buy two zips before I buy a new phone it's sad""
"-"	"-4"	"How Do You think? I will soon erase my iphone and update 10.2.1. Jailed. It is difficult change. iPhone6 iOS9.3.3(jailed) #jailbreak #iphone""
"0"	"0"	"@DizzyForRzeznik iphone 6 same carrier too""
"0"	"0"	"I will probably get a new iPhone today and I still haven't decided which color ???????????? I really need help or at least emotional support""
"0"	"0"	"@ALKAFFARYGROUP  iPhone ..? 7#??????_???????_??_????_???????""
"0"	"0"	"@PrabinSpkt iPhone 7 and 7+ are out in red color.""
"0"	"0"	"@daltonb330 no an iPhone >:(""
"+"	"2"	"@SMARTCares Hi! I'm already out of contract for my iPhone 6+. Can I have it unlocked? (I'm giving it to my brother kasi). Thanks""
"0"	"0"	"My mom borrowed my iPhone charger earlier and forgot to give it back.... soooooo I had to switch to my Galaxy ?""
"0"	"0"	"@ALKAFFARYGROUP  iPhone 7#??????_???????_??_????_???????""
"-"	"-1"	"@Apple My phone has been acting up ? pls send me a iPhone 6s Plus for my inconvenience thx""
"0"	"0"	"The pros otherwise cons speaking of iphone 5: jnPhHq""
"0"	"0"	"Goodbyyyyye fake iphone 7 plus !! @giveawayjusa""
"0"	"0"	"Should I fix my screen? Or get a new iPhone? ?""
"0"	"0"	"@Zollotech @apple @briantong I strongly agree and I think many many more as well. Give us a Red and black iPhone 7/7plus#redandblackiphone7""
"-"	"-3"	"The sacrifices iPhone 7 and 7+ users on 10.1.1 have to make to get the jb working pain in the ass having to re install anemone every reboot""
"0"	"0"	"iphone style only 5k, isi? nya liat di pic""
"0"	"0"	"17 hundred on the cougar sonic run... and 3 Hundo for a brand new iPhone 7 plus all today""
"-"	"-1"	"i'm so beyond mad there is a red iphone when i just bought a damn pink one?????""
"0"	"0"	"Talk about stand up comedy in the age of the iPhone not to mention the Iwatch""
"+"	"2"	"Gosh!!! Red iPhone looks damn nice!!!??????????????""
"+"	"1"	"THANK GOD FOR LOST MY IPHONE""
% of Pos Sentence = 16% of Neg Sentence = 20% of Obj Sentence = 64